

# Yohannes Beneberu

## Web Developer

Hello, I'm Yohannes, I'm a computer science and engineering graduate with a strong interest in problem solving and coding. I'm passionate about coding, problem solving, and researching on new technologies and I spent much of my time in coding and finding out best approaches and practices of system design and implementation.

## **Contact Info**

- +251-934-7879
- jo-ui.github.io/portfolio
- t.me/jhonny\_be
- Addis Ababa, Ethiopia

#### **Education**

#### Adama Science & Technology University

Computer Science & Engineering 2017 - 2022

#### **Skills**

#### **Front End Development**

React.js, Tailwind, Bootstrap, pug...

#### **Back End Development**

Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Mongoose...

# **Graphics Design**

Adobe Illustrator, photoshop & premiere

# **Work Experience**

- Internship at Vintage Technology 2020
  - Develop employee management system using MERN stack
  - Learn advanced javascript and practice on projects
  - Practice graphic design using Adobe illustrator
- Pixel technology

2021 - 2022

- Develop Rental management system for building owners
- Develop website for the company
- provide web application development training for ICT directorate staffs
- Maintain and add features for in office and online applications of the company
- Mobile application testing at Adika Taxi 2019 - 2021
  - Quality testing of Adika taxi passenger and driver apps

#### For More Information



This Barcode
Redirects to My
Personal Website